Thank you for watching subtitles!
Wanchubu, Saipo!
Let's dance the night away, I've made a wish, the future is here
I'll make it through the tender days and the nostalgic days
I'll make it through all the days of the past and the days ahead
The dance of instinct, the authenticity of proof, that's how we prove our existence
Let's dance till the end of time, and make a wish for the future.
I'll make it through the tender days and the nostalgic days
I'll do my best!
I'll do my best today!
I'm looking forward to it!
Here we go!
Come on!
Leave it to me.
Good morning.
Let's all have a good night's sleep while we're at it.
Today is my 7th birthday, so I'd like to make it a grand one.
Now please move on to the next one.
Great!
Next person.
Hello.
I haven't applied foundation yet, so I'll go a little deeper.
I'm at Toyosu Pet today.
Well, it's my one-man show.
Today is my 7th anniversary one-man show, so I'm really nervous.
I don't have a heavy feeling though.
I don't have any heavy feeling.
Happy 7th anniversary, Staff! Congratulations to the staff and congratulations to us! I'm going to do my best with a happy feeling.
I'm off to the rehearsal.
Rehearsal.
It's me.
Wow!
Is it good?
It's so tiny!
Isn't it amazing? I was just hiding.
Yeah, you were hiding right there.
It's tiny!
I'll do my best!
Turtles are strong!
Thank you!
Why?
Why is it so windy?
I'll do my best!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Good morning, Screwsback!
Good morning to all of you.
Thank you for joining us this morning.
Our world cutter.
My name is Wasato.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's nice to meet you.
I look forward to working with you.
Masaki Mizumura
Somewhere, we are going to make a proof of existence.
Red BET-TBSCRIBE
DESQ creat
Please match the lighting only for the last kachichi.
We had a 4 member lineup in January, and then we had been jam-packed with the release period of Miraival Dance until today.
So, we had to keep learning new songs, or rather, relearning the formations of the existing songs.
So, we had to keep learning and performing.
It's a strange feeling that this is the first time for the four of us to celebrate our anniversary together.
It's hard to make up for the difference between the 7th anniversary and the big number, since I'm still going back to the basics, but I'm really looking forward to it.
But I am really looking forward to it.
I think I'm getting really good at formations, or rather, remembering choreography.
I think I've gotten really good at learning formations and choreography.
Personally, after last year's graduation live and this year's live with the new organization, I think I have become much stronger mentally.
I think I have become much stronger mentally.
I used to get nervous before the show.
I used to get nervous before the show, but now I feel like I have to stand up with confidence.
I have more strength, or a strong feeling, to stand up with confidence.
So I don't feel as nervous today as I have in the past.
I think that I am more confident now than before.
I think everyone in Fanship is probably the most anxious about the fact that there will be four of us.
I knew that everyone in FURSHIP would be the most anxious about the four of us becoming a new group, or would feel lonely, so I wanted to be strong.
I wanted to be strong.
I didn't want to show them my anxiety.
So I thought I didn't want to show them my insecurities, and I think that's probably why I felt that way.
I think that's why I can stand up with a strong feeling even though there are four of us.
It is a little different from how I usually feel at our anniversary concerts.
I think it was the unveiling of the four-member lineup in January, or something like that.
We are full of energy.
I think we will be able to deliver a fun live performance from this point on.
I think we will be able to deliver fun live performances from this point on, so I feel like we will start from this point.
This is the second one-man show since we became a four-piece band.
We have been performing live often.
Some of the songs we are playing are new this time, and some of them have changed their positions.
some of the songs we are going to play are new, and some of the songs we are going to play in a different position.
I am worried about that.
I am worried, but I think everyone is moving with an awareness of the overall situation.
I am getting nervous.
I'm really nervous.
I don't know, I don't know.
I didn't really feel it this time, even yesterday.
But when I came here today and rehearsed, I was shaking.
So, I am nervous, but I think it's a good nervousness.
I consider it a good nervousness.
I will do my best.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you all day.
I look forward to working with you.
Please do.
I'll do my best.
What's wrong?
I feel like I've done one show.
Today we have one and two parts, so I used the same amount of energy for one rehearsal, but I'm going to do my best.
I think I am still in good health, so I will do my best. I am fine.
It was a rehearsal.
I feel like I've already finished one more performance.
It's like I'm going to do my best for the second part.
I'm looking forward to it, and the set is soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo effective.
Thank you for watching.
This is Toyosu.
Many hours, too.
Don't tell me.
Are you into rap?
Toyosu.
Today's time is numerous.
I only said two.
Many.
I'll do my best.
I don't like it.
We'll do bettya bread today.
And there are four of us.
It's sticky, sticky, sticky.
We'll do sticky pancakes.
Miri!
NANASE!
Mirika!
Wow!
Hello!
Okay, let's go.
All right!
Let's go!
Eighth year, let's go!
Eighth year.
Please.
I'll do my best.
But seriously, today is the live show where I'm going to do my best.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm just kidding around with the intermission video, so I'm not sure how it will be filmed.
I don't know how it will be filmed.
I was hiding in the video until the very last minute.
But when I saw the audience through the gap
I could see from their faces and the atmosphere that they were really looking forward to the show.
So I got up on stage with the intention of performing in a way that would exceed their expectations and expectations.
I was so moved by the scenery that I started to enjoy myself.
This is Misato Matsuda from the 22nd Watakku Quiz.
We have a tie.
Next up is Watak Chance.
The title of the single song that will be the 4th barsta is
Hiro Chaos, Highest Grade Paradox.
Correct.
Oh...
Okay. The rest.
I've changed.
I've changed, and we're on to the next song.
I'm in my pink fluffy outfit, so I'll try to change it up a bit.
Thank you, everyone. You're so beautiful.
It was so beautiful.
Wow, it's been seven years.
You don't need a microphone.
I've been thinking about it more and more every time I've done a live event at Dos Pit.
I'm sure it would be great to be here as a one-man show.
I was trying to see all the people in the back of the stage, and I was trying to deliver the message that I'm blind.
I'm telling you the truth, my eyesight improves a lot when I'm performing live.
When I perform live, I can see each and every one of you, which makes it even more fun.
I was happy to see the audience in the back of the stage today.
Okay, I'll do my best.
2600 set.
Thank you, audience!
Thank you for your hard work.
I looked up toward the sky
Far and near, the graph is released
shiny and shimmering
Walking into the future today
I remember over and over again
The path of my dreams
There it is! Thank you!
Wow, I was so dead, now
It was fun.
Thank you so much!
Strawberry Foley!
I can't stop thinking about how much fun it is to perform live.
I'm in the middle of an adrenaline rush right now...
But yes, I'm like...
January 10th? At the beginning of this year
I was so nervous about the first one-man show with the four of us.
I was already experiencing the tension of being the first one-man show with 4 members.
I can't say that I'm not used to it.
I can't say I'm not used to it.
I can't make excuses.
The same goes for the songs we've done as 4 members.
and the new songs we've released.New songs, new songs that we have released.
You have to own it all.
I wanted to do a live show where I can proudly say that this is the best one-man show
I wanted to have a live show where I could proudly say that this is the best one-man show
I think I was able to do it.
The moment we finished the first part, I felt like we couldn't do the second part again.
I felt a great sense of accomplishment.
I felt like I was able to give it my all.
But there were people who came only for the second part.
But there were people who came only for the second part, and there were people who were seeing the second part for the first time.
When I thought about that, I suddenly changed my mind.
I'm now determined to do a live show that surpasses the first part.
Right now, everyone is in the venue.
I'm really nervous when I see the video.
I want everyone who came today and those who are watching the streaming to say that it was the best live performance ever.
I hope we can give you a great live performance so that you can say it was the best one yet.
I hope I can deliver a great live performance so that everyone who comes today and those who are watching the video will say it was the best live performance they've ever seen.
And since it's my birthday, I'm going to do my best to enjoy myself as well.
I'll do my best without forgetting to entertain everyone.
Oh, no!
I've been hearing a lot of "Isn't this not good? There are a lot of "Isn't this not good enough?
I've been asking myself "Isn't this not good? I know...
"Isn't this not good?
Oh, that's too much.
This is not so bad, is it?
You're right, you're right.
It's okay, it's okay.
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there.
Miri.
Mai.
Let's do it!
Is it real?
That's amazing!
Tiny.
One is big.
Oh!
Fire.
Red participle
hemp weave
grows
Oh!
I changed early.
Yes, I did. Here is the main story.
I'm off.
Butt touch.
Ariana touch!
Butt touch!
Kakimashimu!
Hit it baby!
Just wave your hands!
Let's go! Wave your hands!
And let's go!
Don't dance!
Be with each other!
And let's go!
I feel like we're going to meet.
Kick it!
Let's go!
Put your hand on your path
Let's do it from here!
It's impossible!
I'm gonna get it!
The past three months have flown by so fast since the beginning of this year.
I've seen so many changes in the past year that it feels as if the 6th anniversary concert a year ago was only recently.
There have been so many things that I have had to deal with flexibly.
I have been struggling to catch up every day, so I thought I would give myself a break after today's performance.
So I would like to give myself a pat on the back after today's performance.
I hope to be able to work hard for the tour.
How full are you tonight?
Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh
You're not going for a while
No No No No
Before I knew it, I had a dream
Into the mysterious streets
Even though no one can chase after what I love
I'll be finished in three minutes.
I'm going to enjoy myself.
That things don't go the way you want them to.
Let's try to keep it.
Happy Happy To you
Happy, happy, happy for me.
You can't give me perfection alone, can you?
All that glitters
You can't keep defending what's not enough
The clock never stops
The end, the end, the clock never stops
If someone keeps the song flying
Even the dreams will pass
I'm sure I can see a continuation that I don't know
I hold out my hand to you, and the end
It's still screaming to go on
Goodbye, hello to you and me
The way you sing
Thank you!
Our 7th anniversary is over!
Thank you very much!Thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
It was great. It was really cool.
I liked the side view.
He turned his head to the side and showed a lot of face that people couldn't see.
Generational change.
It could have been anyone.
So, I'm very energetic, but I'm pretty sore because I gave it all I had.
My body hurts.
I couldn't get my back up.
Really.
Generational change. Everyone.
But, the 7th anniversary has come and gone.
It's early. Really.
To the 7th anniversary.
Barna also knows that it's only 8 years.
I just said 8 years.
That's scary. I don't want to say too much.
I don't want to say that.
I said it in secret.
Eight years of secrecy.
Infinite?
You are infinite.
I realize it's the other way around.
I wondered if you were attached to the 8th anniversary infinity, and I found out that the 8th anniversary is also difficult.
Eighth anniversary.
You are infinity this year.
Let's make this a year of infinity.
There are so many possibilities.
So I thought today would be it.
It's been a while.
On the day of the 7th year, you will be a first-class ten-thousand-fold person.
That's right.
Like tension B.
It's amazing.
It's amazing!
That's infinity.
Do you want to go to infinity today?
Yes.
Worcester infinity.
Infinite Worcester.
I see. Infinite Worcester.
One and marshmallow infinity.
Long.
Infinity.
The end.
Enter the stage and the end.
It's infinite. If it spreads out.
It's been 8 years now, and we've already decided to go on tour.
We're going to work hard on recording and distributing singles for the summer.
We will continue to deliver the music, so please look forward to it! We will do our best!
We will do our best!
Thank you for your continued support.
Thank you very much.
I can't stop thanking you.
I can't stop.
Ah.
Glasses.
Infinite? Infinite?
Still infinite.